Finding Aid for the John Thomas McGill Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
John Thomas McGill Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0276
5.46 linear_feet
This collection contains the papers of John Thomas McGill (1851-1946), longtime faculty member and Dean of the School of Pharmacy at Vanderbilt. He also served as Secretary and Treasurer of the Tennessee Academy of Science for 15 years.
Scope and Contents Note
This collection contains the papers of John Thomas McGill (1851-1946), longtime faculty member and Dean of the School of Pharmacy at Vanderbilt. He also served as Secretary and Treasurer of the Tennessee Academy of Science for 15 years.
Other materials in the collection:
Holograph Articles
Appreciation of Edward Emerson Barnard
College of Pharmacy Degrees
Department of Pharmacy
The Four Years’ Experience Prerequisite
The Increasing Responsibilities of the Pharmacist
The Qualifications for Licensure Required by Law Determine the Standard of Pharmaceutical Education
The Relation of the American Conference of Pharmaceutical Faculties to the National Association of Boards of Pharmacy with Reference to the Educational Prerequisite for the Practice of Pharmacy
What Degrees Should Be Conferred by Schools of Pharmacy?
Untitled
Articles by Mcgill
High Schools in the Southern States
The Locality Educational Proviso
The New York State and Boston Proposition with Respect to Degrees
A Resolution in Regard to Pharmaceutical Degrees - 6 copies
The Tennessee Academy of Science
Vanderbilt School of Pharmacy - 4 copies
What Degrees Should be Conferred by Schools of Pharmacy? - 4 copies
2 Untitled
1 fragment
Miscellaneous
One-page partial report by McGill; two pages from Tennessee Pharmaceutical Association; Hendrix College Bulletin, 1916; lists of names; material in German; minutes of Summer School Faculty Meeting, March 4, 1901; Dept. of Pharmacy Graduation Certificate; Excursion Announcement; Holograph report of School of Pharmacy, 1917-1918; Information of U. S. High Schools. Questionnaire; Final Exam, Pharmacy 1916. poem.
A Chronology
1851 Born in Monroe County, Tennessee
1877 Principal of Bentonville High School
1879 B. S., Vanderbilt University
1880 President, Vanderbilt Alumni Association
1880-1890 Secretary, Dept. of Pharmacy
1881 PhD., Vanderbilt Uiversity and member of faculty
1882 PhG degree, Vanderbilt University
1882 Historian of Vanderbilt Alumni Association
1885-1886 Year of study at University of Berlin, Germany
1892 President of Vanderbilt Alumni Fund Committee
1892-1893 Chairman, Alumni Association Executive Committee which organized the Alumni Fund
1893 Married Lizzie Allen of Harrisonville, Missouri
1900 Full Professor
1901 Phi Beta Kappa - Secretary, Vanderbilt Chapter. Continued in this office until his death.
1919 Retired as Emeritus Professor of Organic Chemistry
1925-1939 Secretary and treasurer of Tennessee Academy of Science
1932 Tennessee Academy of Science names biological building at Reelfoot Lake after McGill. Establishment of this station in 1931 was a·result of McGill’s efforts.
1939 Retirement as secretary-treasurer of Tennessee Academy of Science; elected honorary president of life.
1944 Published The Vanderbilt Chapter of Phi Beta Kappa, 1901-1943
April 11, 1946 Died at home on Vanderbilt campus
Dates uncertain: Dean of School of Pharmacy for fifteen years, Member of IV Club, Old Oak Club.
Source: Vanderbilt Alumnus, June, 1946
- Container List
  - Correspondence - Outgoing. Chronologically arranged. Undated placed last. (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  - Incoming. A-Cushing. (Box 1, Folder 7-20)
  - Dake-Lane, A. V. (through July 28, 1884). (Box 2, Folder 21-42)
  - Lane, A. V. (Aug. 4, 1884 -- ) - Rust (Box 3, Folder 43-61)
  - Saalbach-illegible (Box 4, Folder 62-76)
  - Centennial Circular - Correspondence. (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Letters Concerning extraneous matters. Topics include inquiries about entrance requirements into school of pharmacy, requests for information, etc. Arranged alphabetically by sender. (Box 5, Folder 78-83)
  - Summer School Bulletin Correspondence. (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Holograph Notes - Notes by McGill and others on various topics. The name “Joy Crunn11 is signed on one sheet. (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Holograph Articles - Arranged alphabetically. (Box 5, Folder 86-87)
  - Reports - Dean of Pharmacy. 1901-1919. Holograph. (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Reports on Ducktown Sulphur Copper and Iron Co. Concerns air pollution. Charts and analyses, legal documents, business receipts, reports, newspaper clippings. (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Business Records - invoices, bills, receipts. (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Charts and Graphs (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Circulars - form letters and cards - incoming and outgoing. (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Prospective Student Data (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Pictures - Garland Bust. 36 pictures. (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Garland Memorial - planning and fund raising material, invoices, contract between Alumni Association and sculptor. (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Garland Memorial Fund - one checkbook. (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Summer School - Receipts and Business Papers. (Box 6, Folder 97-98)
  - Records and Facts of University History. (Box 6, Folder 99-101)
  - Faculty - Holograph lists of faculty members. (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Faculty of Law Dept. and Biblical Dept. (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Faculty of Academic Dept. - Biographical Information. (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Lists of Faculty and Students - Dept. of Pharmacy and Dentistry. (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Admission Applications - School of Pharmacy (Box 6, Folder 106-107)
  - Addresses (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Class Lists - Engineering, Academic, Biblical, Dental Dept. and graduate students. (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Alumni - Academic Dept. - notes up to 1891. (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Alumni - Biblical Dept. (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Alumni - Engineering Dept. (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Alumni - Law Dept. (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Alumni - Dept. of Pharmacy. (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Alumni Assoc. Officers. (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Alumni Assoc. - lists of alumni speakers, minutes of meetings, recrods of dues paid. (Box 7, Folder 116-118)
  - Alumni Poems - 4 items. (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Pamphlets - Alumni Association - Alumni Address, Constitution and By-Laws, Executive Committee Reports. (Box 7, Folder 120-122)
  - Vanderbilt Alumni Fund Assoc. Checkbook. (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Barnard Club. Information such as mailing lists, financial record, newspaper clipping, lectures. (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Memorials (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Applications - recognition and accrediting of Pharmacy Schools. (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Articles by McGill - typescript and printed. Alphabetically arranged. (Box 8, Folder 127-128)
  - Reprints by McGill - alphabetically arranged. (Box 8, Folder 129-133)
  - Information about McGill. pages from The Bulletin of Pharmacy and from American Druggist and Pharmaceutical Record, The Pharmaceutical Era and one page of typescript. (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Miscellaneous - see other page for description. (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Pamphlets - M.E. Church and Vanderbilt - 5 items. (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - Articles by Others - “Pharmaceutical Education” by Otto A. Wall. (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - Papers by Others Frank Butenshon, “Action of Light on Chanicals and Pharmaceuticals”; Charles Cason, “Alumni Trustees in American Universities Methods of Obtaining Expression of Alumni Opinion and Wishes in the Selection of Trustees - Postal Ballot”; W. H. Witt “The Bishops and the Carnegie Gift.” parti’(al article “The Development of Civic Improvement in Tennessee” (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Reprints by Others:, R. F. Chew “The Ends We Aim At” E. I. Crockett “Schiller’s ‘Lay of the Bell’” - 2 copies. Duncan U. Fletcher, “What Will He Do With It?” Percy W. Gardner “The Agencies of Our National Progress” G. C. Jones “The Impress of Thought” - 2 copies. A. V. Lane “Note on a Roulette” Henry N. Snyder “Vanderbilt University in Some of Its Relations to Higher Education at the South” (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets - The Student World, Vol. 1, No.3, March 1884. (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - Pictures and Photographs, including: 12 floral picture postcards. one frontispiece of magazine. Group picture: Q BK guests in McGill home -- Edwin Mims, A. Harris, E. Reinke, J. T. McGill, Voorhies, M. Sarratt, Johnson, Little(Peabody); Group picture - Dinner for Dr. Voorhees Q BK; Group picture: Planting of Overcup Oak, Oct. 16, 1925 - Currey Taylor Courtnay, Josephine Elliston Farrell, Clifton Douglas Forde, Susan Litton Gordon; Chikao Kawasaki; Campus scenes; Garland Bust “Moseley’; Dr. and Mrs. J. T. McGill; Dr. McGill, Dr. Dudley, Dr. Hollinshed; unidentified. (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - Books - Memorandum Book. (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - Summer School Record Book. 1894-1902. (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - Printed Books - Material dealing with Pharmaceutical Association meetings. Commercial Press, Ltd., a handbook. (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Printed Books: A. V. Lane, Adjustments of the Compass, Transit, and Level; J. T. McGill, Laboratory Experiments in General Chemistry; Emil Otto, German Reader. (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - Entire box contains programs, announcements, and invitations. (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Programs Alumni Association (Box 10, Folder 145-146)
  - Programs - Class Day (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Programs - Cole Lectures (Box 10, Folder 148)
  - Programs - Commencement (Box 10, Folder 149-150)
  - Programs - Concerts (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Programs - Debate Societies (Box 10, Folder 152-153)
  - Programs - Founder’s Medal Contest (Box 10, Folder 154)
  - Programs - Literary Societies (Box 10, Folder 155-156)
  - Programs - Oratorical Contest (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Programs - Philosophic Literary Society (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Programs - Vanderbilt - 25th Anniversary (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Programs - Woman’s Club (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Programs - YMCA (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Announcements - Biblical Dept. (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Announcements - Vanderbilt (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Announcements and Invitations - Vanderbilt Moot Court (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Programs and Announcements - Vanderbilt Events (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - Invitations - Senior Dinner (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Social Invitations (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Invitations and Programs - Non-Vanderbilt (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - Box contains newspaper and magazine clippings. Clippings are arranged by topic alphabetically. (Box 11, Folder 169-186)
  - Pharmacy Club Book of Minutes, Location: M/4/9 (Box Separate)
- List of Clipping Topics, Several articles are often pasted on one page. The term item indicates each separate page of articles. If an article is carried over on more than one page, then these pages are considered one item.
  - A
    - Alexander, Dr. Gross (Methodist editor)
    - Alumni, Vanderbilt - 2 items (including Alumni Memorial Hall)
    - Anderson, Major Glenn P. (ROTC Commandant)
    - Anniversary, Vanderbilt’s Twenty-fifth - 7 items
    - Atchison, Dr. Thomas A.
    - Austral, Story of Vanderbilt
  - B
    - Baccalaureate - Bishop Nicholson
    - Baccalaureate Dr. J. W. Lee
    - Baccalaureate - Dr. John A. Broadus, 3 items.
    - Barnard, Edward Emerson - 4 items (astronomer)
    - Barton, Dr. William E. (theology professor)
    - Baskervill, Mrs. Janie McTyeire
    - Baskervill, William M. - 3 items. (English professor) One article by him on “Vanderbilt University”“)
    - Baxter, Judge Edmund D. - 2 items (law professor)
    - Baxter, Nathaniel - 2 items (lawyer, state senator)
    - Bell, Vanderbilt campus
    - Bennie, George E.
    - Biblical Dept. of Vanderbilt
    - Billmeyer, U. D. (dental professor)
    - Board of Trust - 7 items
    - Briggs, Charles S. (medical professor)
    - Broun, William LeRoy
    - Brown, C. S. - 2 items (engineering professor)
    - Brown, J. P. W. (Nashville businessman)
    - Burch, Charles N.
    - Burch, Robert L. (Nashville businessman)
    - Byrd, C. W. (Methodist minister)
  - c
    - Callender, Dr. J. H. (medical professor)
    - Campus scenes - 6 items
    - Carmichael, O. C. (Chancellor, Vanderbilt)
    - Cason, Charles - 2 items (alumni secretary)
    - Cattell, Dr. D.M. (dental professor)
    - Cayce, Dr. Eldred B. (medical professor
    - Chappell, E. B. - 2 items (Methodist minister, editor)
    - Clark, Sam L. (medical professor)
    - Class Day
    - Class Day Promenade (1899)
    - Class Dinner 1912
    - Class Reunion (1896)
    - Clock, Vanderbilt - Kirkland Hall
    - Cole, Col. and Mrs. E. W. - 4 items
    - Cole Lectures
    - Cole, Whitefoord R. 2 items
    - Commencement - 16 items (1892-1934)
    - Commencement - University of Kentucky
    - Commodores Banquet (1907)
    - Conwell, Mrs. Martha Soule (matron, Wesley Hall)
    - Cooper, James Thomas (student)
    - Crawford, James Y. (dental professor)
    - Crenshaw, Hervey Files (lawyer, alumnus)
    - Dawson, Dr. ? (lecturer)
    - Denny, Collins(philosopher, professor, bishop, etc.)
    - Dentistry, School of
    - Depew, Chauncy M. - 2 items
    - Dewey Cannon, painting of (1900)
    - Dickinson, Jacob M. - 2 items (lawyer, judge)
    - Dolliver, Hon. J. P. (speaker)
    - Douglas, David
    - Douglas, Dr. Richard (medical professor)
    - Dudley, W. L. - 6 items (chemistry and medical dean)
    - Duncan, William Wallace - 2 items (Methodist Bishop)
    - Dunn, Dr. Ross (medical professor)
    - Dyer, Gus A.
  - E
    - East, Judge Edward Hazzard (president, Board of Trust)
    - Edgerton, John
    - Engineering Hall (dedication, 1888)
    - Endowment Campaign 1928 - 16 items
    - Eve, Duncan (medical professor)
    - Eve, Dr. Paul F. - 2 items (medical professor)
    - Ewing, William Green (medical dean)
  - F
    - Fifth Avenue Hotel (closing of 1895)
    - Fite, Col. Thomas D. (Nashville businessman)
    - Flexnor, Abraham (Lectureship)
    - Football Game, Fights at (1896)
    - Founder’s Day Contest
    - Founder’s Day Dinners
    - Freeman, Dr. R. R. (dental professor)
    - Fulton, John (“Uncle Remus”) - 2 items
    - Furman, Frazier
    - Furman, Mary J.
    - Furman Hall - 3 items
  - G
    - Gallaway, C. B. (bishop, president, Board of Trust)
    - Garland, Landon Cabell - 9 items
    - Gilder, Dr. Richard Watson - 2 items (literary address)
    - Glenn, Dr. L. C. (geology professor, iris-grower)
    - Granberry, John Cowper - 2 items (bishop, theology professor)
    - Graves, Herschel A.
    - Gray, Pleasant
  - H
    - Haden, Mrs. T. H. (Jennie Conwell - Methodist missionary)
    - Haggard, Dr. William David (medical professor)
    - Hall, Allen Garland - 5 items (law dean)
    - Hall, Fitzgerald- 4 items (president, N.C. & St. L.; law professor; Board of Trust)
    - Hamberlin, Lafayette R. - English professor
    - Hambleton, Dr. B. F. (medical professor; acting medical dean)
    - Hargrove, Harriet C.
    - Hargrove, Robert Kenner - 4 items
    - Hart, Henry G. (S. C. A. secretary)
    - Hendrix, E.R. - 3 items (bishop, presieent of Board of Trust)
    - Hillman, T. T. (Nashville businessman)
    - Hoge, Moses D.
    - Hospital, Vanderbilt - First Board of Managers
    - Hume, Alfred - 3 items (math professor, president, University of Mississippi)
  - J
    - Jackson, Nat Baxter
    - Jones, Sam
    - Joynes, Edward S. - 4 items
    - Judd, J. W.
  - K
    - Kawasaki, Chikao
    - Keeble, John Bell - 2 items
    - Keith, Samuel J. - 2 items
    - Kelley, D.C. - 3 items
    - Kellogg, James C. - 2 items
    - Kesler, John L.
    - Kessler, George E.
    - King, J. M.
    - Kirkland, Chancellor James H. - 12 items
    - Kirkland, Marion
  - L
    - Lambuth, W. R.
    - Law School
    - Lawrence, John H.
    - Leech, Mrs. James M.
    - Leech, J. M.
    - Lees, R. B.
    - Lipscomb, Andrew Agate
    - Litterer, William
    - Locke, H. A.
    - Lowry, John
    - Lupton, Kate
    - Lurton, H. H. - 3 items
  - M
    - · Maddin, Thomas L.
    - Main Building - 17 items
    - Malone, Thomas H.
    - Manchester, Paul T. - 2 items
    - Marshall, Charles Yun
    - Martin, G. W.
    - McAlister, W. K. - 5 items
    - McGill, J. T.
    - McKee, J. W.
    - McNeilly, R. H. - 6 items
    - McReynolds, James c.
    - McTyeire, Holland N. - 4 items
    - Medical Dept. - 3 items
    - Menees, Orville H.
    - Merrill, Austin H.
    - Moon, The
    - Moose, William L.
    - Moot Court - 2 items
    - Morgan, Henry W. - 5 items
  - N
    - Nichol, W. L.
    - Neely Auditorium
  - O
    - Orr, Polly
  - P
    - Paine, Robert
    - Peabody College - 4 items
    - Pharmaceutical Dept. - 4 items
    - Pharmaceutical Meetings, National - 2 items
    - Pharmacy, Bulletin of, Clippings - 4 pages
    - Price, George H.
  - Q
    - Quarterly, Vanderbilt
  - R
    - Radcliffe, W. C.
    - Regulations for Vanderbilt
    - Robinson, Dr. G. Canby - 6 items
    - Rodgers, Woodall
    - ROTC, Navel
    - Ruddiman, E.A.
    - Religion, School of, Faculty 1931-32, 1881-82
    - Rodriguez, P. A. - 3 items
  - S
    - Safford, James H. - 2 items
    - Sarratt, C. M.
    - Shearer, John L.
    - Shinnick, Ed D.
    - Sloan, George A.
    - Smith, A. Coke - 3 items
    - Smith, Charles F.
    - South Campus Clinic
    - Stahlman, James G.
    - Steger, Robert W.
    - Stokes, Walter
    - Stubblefield, D. R.
    - Sullivan, W. V.
    - Summers, Thomas Osgood
    - Summers, Thomas Osmond
    - Sumpter, J. Rhea
  - T
    - Tigert, John J. - 9 items
    - Tillett, Wilbur Fisk - 5 items
  - V
    - Valentine’s Homeric Group
    - Valentine’s Jefferson
    - Van Dyke, Henry J.
    - Vanderbilt, Cornelius - 2 items
    - Vanderbilt, W. K.
    - Vanderbilts, Endowments Given by
    - Vaughn, William J. - 2 items
    - Vanderbilt University - 2 folders
  - W
    - Waller, Judge Claude - 3 items
    - Ward, Gus K. - 2 items
    - Ward, Seth - 2 items
    - Weaver, Thomas S.
    - Wesley Hall - 4 items
    - West, Anson
    - West, Olin
    - Wharton, C.
    - White, Horace H. - 2 items
    - Whitworth, J. Leonard
    - Wilbur, Charles H.
    - Wiley, Edwin
    - Williams, Wils - 3 items
    - Wilson, D. T., Dr.
    - Wilson, Woodrow
    - Winton, G. B. - 2 items
    - Witherspoon, John A. - 2 items
  - Y
    - Young, R. A. - 2 items
    - Yun, T. H. (Yun Chi Ho) - 2 items
    - Yun, Helen
  - Z
    - Zdanowicz, Casimir - 2 items
- Correspondence List - Outgoing
  - H.N. McTyeire, 4 May 1886
  - H.N. McTyeire, 5 June 1886
  - H.N. McTyeire, 23 July 1886
  - H.N. McTyeire, 31 July 1888
  - D. C. Kelley, 25 Aug. 1889
  - Sir, --- 188-
  - Sir, --- 1893(?)
  - Sir, 22 Feb. 1893
  - W. T. Lupton, 9 March 1893
  - Sir, 4 Oct.1895
  - American Express Co., 2 April 1897
  - W.H. Witt, 8 Nov. 1897
  - W. B. McMullen, 20 Dec. 1897
  - Board of Trust, 19 June 1899
  - Percy Maddin, 26 Feb. 1907
  - C. S. N. Hallberg, 19 Aug. 1908
  - Robert C. Wilson, 11 Nov. 1908
  - Sir, 1 Dec. 1908
  - E. J. Kennedy, 18 Dec. 1908
  - C. H. Orr, 19 Dec. 1908
  - Doctor, Gordon, Sam, 21 Jan. 1909 (3)
  - Sir, ___ Jan. 1909
  - Alfred Howell, W. B. Taylor, 28 Jan. 1909 (2)
  - John Bell Keeble, 24 May 1909
  - L. N. Gibbert, 16 March 1910
  - W. H. Blome, 16 April 1910
  - Claude E. Cannon, 12 Aug. 1910
  - H. H. Rushy, 14 Aug. 1912
  - J. H. Kirkland, 9 June 1913
  - J. H. Kirkland, 5 June 1914
  - E. F. Turner, 30 Sept.1914
  - J. H. Kirkland, 6 May 1915
  - Thomas H. McAdams, W. G. McAdams, 13 March 1916 (2)
  - P. A. Mandabach, 9 Nov. 1916
  - J. T. Spalding, 9 Oct. 1918
  - J. H. Kirkland, 28 May 1919
  - J. H. Kirkland, 5 June 1919
  - James Walton, 15 June 1920
  - Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Chemistry, 3 Nov. 1920
  - Glenn D. Skinner, 8 May 1921
  - E. E. Barnard, 26 June 1921
  - To the Bresident, 17 July 1922
  - Mary R. Calvert, 15 Aug. 1924
  - George McP. Smith, 16 Feb. 1925
  - H. C. Hibbs, 29 June 1925
  - J. L. Farnum, 27 March 1926
  - Mr. and Mrs. Frances P. Garvan, 22 March 1929
  - Emmett B. Carmichael, 10 Aug. 1931
  - John Howe Yoe, 30 June 1932
  - G. M. Bentley, 27 March 1934
  - D. U. Fletcher, 3 Sept. 1934
  - J. McKeen Cattell, 2 May 1935
  - Charles L. Parsons, 21 Nov. 1935
  - Elizabeth Baskervill Wall, 21 May 1936
  - 2 unaddressed, 1 fragment; 1 to “Gentlemen”; 1 to “Sir”, n.d
Index to Incoming Correspondence
(Addressee, unless otherwise noted, is John Thomas McGill.)
Ackland, William Hayes (1) -- n.d.
Adams, Herbert (1) -- n.d.
Alcorn, Clara F. (2) -- 6 May 1903; 26 Dec 1917
Alexander, Gross (1) -- 13 June 1888
American Druggist Publishing Co. (1) -- 1 Jul 1910
American-French Perfume Co. (1) -- 8 Feb 1915
American Zinc Co. (1) -- 26 July 1899
Ancrum, J.H. (1) -- 26 July 1899
Anderstog, James T. (1) -- l Oct 1896
Andrews, D.T. (2) -- 19, 22 Mar 1906
Armstrong, John K. (1) -- 26 Aug 1 96
Arnold, B.W., Jr. (1) -- 13 Jan 1923
Arny, Henry Vinecome (2) -- 25 May 1 96; 22 May 1897
Atlee, James H. (1) -- 22 Aug 1887
Austin, H.W. (1) -- 8 Dec 1896
Austin, W.R. (2) -- 30 June, 11 July 1911
Ayres, Albert J. (2) -- 2 Oct 1907; 20 July 1908
Babcock, S.H. (1) -- 30 Oct 1900
Bachman, Gustav (1) -- 14 Feb 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Bailey, F.J. (4) -- 22 June, 5 Aug (2)-1915; 3 May 1916
Bailey, H.T. (1) -- 13 Feb 1909
Bain, Samuel M. (5) -- 31 July, 30 Sept, 6 Oct 1915; 13 Mar, 6 Nov 1916
Banks, L.F. (1) -- 21 Feb 1893
Barclay, W.F. (2) -- 19 Aug 1890; n.d. (to D.M. Smith)
Barnard, Edward Emerson (12) -- 22 Sept 1891; 22, 29 Apr 1895; June 1898; 15 Oct 1900; 1 Feb 1901; 13 Feb 1904; 30 June, 13, 22 July 1921; 11 Mar 1922; n.d. (frag.)
Barnitt(?), J.B. (1) -- 16 July 1920
Barrett, John (1) -- 15 Dec 1908 (to Robert L. Burch)
Barthell, Edward E. (2) -- 11, 18 Dec 1908
Barton, George M. (1) -- 3 June 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Baskervill, Janie McTyeire (14) -- 25 Jan 1928; 30 July, 10, 30 Aug 1937; 4 May 1938; 15 Jan, 14, 29, Mar, 4, 19 Apr 1939 (all to Mrs. McGill); 24 June, 26 July, 4 Oct 1939; 16 Oct 1940
Baskerville, Charles (10) -- 2 July, 12, 19 Aug 1891; 10 Oct 1892; 12 Feb, 6 Mar 1893; 12 July, 1 Sept 1894; 25 Nov 1895; 2 May 1916
Bates, W.H. (1) -- 15 Feb 1909 (to J.E. Hart)
Baynard, L.B., Jr. (1) -- 3 Mar 1895
Beal, James H. (6) -- 21 Mar 1896; 17 May 1897; 6 May 1898; 13, 14 Nov 1907; 9 Mar 1908 (see abo Midland)
Beale, George L. (1) -- 17 Feb 1907
Bedford, P.W. (1) - 12 Aug 1891
Bell, J.M. (1) -- 4 Apr 1910
Bemis, H.E. (3) -- 14 May (to C.L. Thornburg), 5 Nov 1895; 6 Feb 1909
Benedict, Samuel C. (2) -- 15, 24 Jan 1907
Bentley, G.M. (1) -- 13 July 1915
Berry, M.F. (1) -- 6 Apr 1897
Bigham, R.J. (3) -- 15 May 1896; 5, 13 Jan 1897
Black, M.M. (1) -- 30 Apr 1895
Boddie, Mary B. (3) -- 28 Sept 1892; 10 Mar 1898; 25 Sept 1925
Bogart, W.G. (1) -- 19 Jan 1907
Bond, ---- (1) -- 10 Dec 1910
Bond, John B., Sr, (2) -- 12 Nov 1913 (to J.C. Simpson); n.d.
Bond, William Jennings (3) -- 10 May, 11 Sept 1917; 11 Oct 1918 (all to E.A. Ruddiman)
Bostick, J.B. (3) -- 4 July 1898; 10 Aug 1922; 17 Dec 1940
Bowron, William M. (5) -- 5 June (2 - 1 to A.M. Shook), 3 July 1915; 12 Apr 1916; n.d.
Brace, DeWitt B. (1) -- 28 Oct 1885
Bradfield, John W. (1) -- 6 Sept 1898
Bradfield, W.D. (1) -- 24 Apr 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Bradley, Q.O. (1) 6 Sept 1897
Bradley, T.O. (1) -- 14 June 1885
Bramlette, E.E. (1) -- 16 July 1922
Brandon, J. (?) A. (1) -- 10 Sept 1891
Brandon, W.H. (1) -- 26 Jan 1920
Brandon Printing Co. (1) -- 9 Jan 1920
Branham, William C. (2) -- 2 June 1898; 10 Apr 1899
Brauner, Edgar J. (1) -- 27 Mar 1920
Brewer, T.H. (1) -- 2 Feb 1909 (to J.E. Hart)
Brockman, F.S. (6) -- 27 May, 7 June, 18 July 1893; 21 May 1894; 8 Apr, 13 June 1895
Broun, W. Leroy (3) -- 12 July 1878; 8, 23 Mar 1922
Browden, R.W. (6) -- 22 May, 2 June 1890; 1 Dec 1893 (to C.L. Thornburg); 15 May 1894 (to C.L. Thornburg); 31 May 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg); 4 Jan 1897
Brown, Calvin S. (4) -- 24 Feb, 4 Mar 1900; 10 Feb 1909; 14 Sept 1911
Brown Chemical Co. (1) -- 6 Nov 1907
Brown, Elmer Ellsworth (1) -- 29 Mar 1910
Brown, James W. (1) -- 10 July 1910
Brown, Lucius P. (2) -- 11, 12 Apr 1910